<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Terra</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="google_map_key">AIzaSyA9vsTnJMlx2j_5UKYUntzqdcsPSmXT86k</string>

    <string name="before_earthquake">
        • Anchor heavy appliances / furniture to the wall. \n \n
        • Make a plan of where to  meet your family after an earthquake. \n \n
        • Make sure you have access to a fire extinguisher, first-aid kit, extra batteries, flashlight, and a battery powered radio. \n \n
        • Get familiar with the earthquake plan at other locations like schools and offices. \n \n
    </string>


    <string name="before_wildfire">
        • Learn how to prevent wildfires (most fires are caused by people usually during the summer months). \n \n
        • Practice safety techniques (stop, drop, and roll). \n \n
        • Make sure home and other belongings are insured. \n \n
        • Prepare an emergency kit which should have three days worth of supplies for each member (water, emergency contacts, first aid, blankets, flashlight, batteries, nonperishable food, battery powered radio). \n \n
        • Create a map and mark emergency exits. \n \n
        • Keep a watch for local news about wildfires around you. \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="during_earthquake">
        • Stay calm! \n \n
        • If you are indoors stay inside and if you are outdoors stay outside. \n \n
        • If you are indoors, stay away from windows and outside doors and instead crawl under heavy furniture or stand against a wall near the center of the building. \n \n
        • If you are outdoors, stay away from power lines, buildings, and anything that might fall. \n \n
        • Don’t use matches or candles because of potentially broken gas lines. \n \n
        • If you are in a car, stop the car and stay inside. \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="during_wildfire">
        • Be prepared to evacuate at any moment (usually a very short notice is given). \n \n
        • Keep a watch of the news and obey officials and authorities. \n \n
        • Consider soaking your entire property in water \n \n
        • Keep windows and doors closed to limit exposure to dust. \n \n
    </string>

    <string name="after_earthquake">
        • Turn on the radio and use phones for emergencies. \n \n
        • Check yourself and others around you for injures and provide first aid to those that need it. \n \n
        • Be careful of broken glass and other objects that may injure you. \n \n
        • Stay away from beaches as tsunamis often hit after the earthquake \n \n
        • Expect potential aftershocks. \n \n
        • Stay away from damaged areas \n \n
        • Check water, electric, and gas lines and if any are damaged, shut off the valves. If the smell of gas is present, open all windows and doors and exit the building.
    </string>

    <string name="after_wildfire">
        • Pack supplies before heading back home such as garbage bags, gloves, goggles, closed toe shoes, and bottled water. \n \n
        • Take pictures of damaged objects to make it easier for the insurance company to track what is damaged. \n \n
        • Enter the house carefully and turn of the main power breaker immediately. \n \n
        • Walk around the perimeter of the house before entering. \n \n
        • Throw any food items out if the house was without power for a long time. \n \n
        • Contact your home insurance broker to get started with repairs right away. \n \n
    </string>
    <string name="risk_score_blurb">Your hazard index is a weighted value calculated based on your location and preparedness.</string>
    <string name="readiness_score_blurb">Your preparation index is calculated based on how many items you have prepared in your emergency kit.</string>
    <string name="risk_score_average">The highest possible hazard index is 1.00. Assuming an average readiness score of 60%, the risk score of someone living near the San Andreas Fault would be 0.48.</string>
    <string name="readiness_score_average">An average preparation index would be around 60%.</string>

    <string name="user_privacy_agreement"> Onyx Jewels may change, suspend, or discontinue the availability of any Terra feature at any time. Onyx Jewels reserves the right to charge fees for future use of or access to the Terra application. Onyx Jewels does not guarantee that Terra is free of inaccuracies, errors, bugs, or interruptions, or is reliable, accurate, complete, or otherwise valid. \n
Disclaimer of Any Warranty: Terra and all data derived through such application are provided \"as is\" with no warranty, express or implied, of any kind and Onyx Jewels expressly disclaims any and all warranties and conditions, including but not limited to, any implied warranty of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, availability, security, title and non-infringement. You are solely responsible for any damage that results from the use of Terra and any data derived through such application including, but not limited to, any damage to your device or loss of data. \n
Limitation of Liability: Onyx Jewels shall not, under any circumstances, be liable to you for any indirect, incidental, consequential, special or exemplary damages arising out of or in connection with use of the Terra application and any data derived through such application, whether based on breach of contract, breach of warranty, tort (including negligence, product liability or otherwise), or any other pecuniary loss, whether or not Onyx Jewels has been advised of the possibility of such damages. Under no circumstances shall Onyx Jewels be liable to you for any amount. \n
Release and Waiver: To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, you hereby release and waive all claims against Onyx Jewels, and its affiliates, officers, agents, or other partners, and employees from any and all liability for claims, damages (actual and/or consequential), costs and expenses (including litigation costs and attorneys\' fees) of every kind and nature, arising from or in any way related to your use of the Terra application and data derived through such application. If you are a California resident, you waive your rights under California Civil Code 1542, which states, \"A general release does not extend to claims which the creditor does not know or suspect to exist in his favor at the time of executing the release, which if known by him must have materially affected his settlement with the debtor.\" You understand that any fact relating to any matter covered by this release may be found to be other than now believed to be true and you accept and assume the risk of such possible differences in fact. In addition, you expressly waive and relinquish any and all rights and benefits which you may have under any other state or federal statute or common law principle of similar effect, to the fullest extent permitted by law. \n
Hold Harmless and Indemnify: To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, you agree to hold harmless and indemnify Onyx Jewels and its officers or other partners, and employees from and against any third-party claim arising from or in any way related to your use of the Terra application and any data derived through the application, including any liability or expense arising from all claims, losses, damages (actual and/or consequential), suits, judgments, litigation costs and attorneys\' fees, of every kind and nature. Onyx Jewels shall use good faith efforts to provide you with written notice of such claim, suit or action. \n
Invalidity of Specific Terms: If any provision of the Terra Application Terms is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties\' intentions as reflected in the provision and that the other provisions remain in full force and effect.
No Waiver of Rights by Onyx Jewels: Onyx Jewels\'s failure to exercise or enforce any right or provision of the Terra Application Terms shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.</string>

</resources>
